it's the afternoon and I that I hadn't
done my video yet because I had no
morning appointment so I'm doing a video
next five minutes or water who will
interrupt so should be interesting
um if you don't know about me I have
chronic fatigue and fibromyalgia and had
brain tumors and usually I've been doing
fairly well because I've managed my
condition my daughters in full-time day
care but this last she's been off her
school doesn't start till September 11th
and her last day was on the the 30th of
August so she's been home a lot more
than usual usually a long weekend wipes
meal for weeks and so this period of
time and she started school in September
11th but I'm expected to go with her for
the first week so it's gonna be a new
adjustment and feeling like I'm not
doing enough for my project even though
I have actually been working on my
project but my mental state isn't in the
best the best condition also today at my
appointment you know are you on your way
to work after and I and I'm like I don't
I don't work and it's true I don't work
and earn a paycheck at least not
currently but this is work this isn't
just but this is one of my events a day
this and meditation which I did manage
to do today and but figuring out I just
been present and listening to what I
need to do for the global cooperative
not holding myself back and not doing
things that I feel like I'm not able to
but also not pushing myself too far and
it's a hard balancing act figure out I
took my daughter to the peony on
don't even know what a first few days it
opened that wasn't the weekend and I'm
still recovering even the last few weeks
of August the last weekend half of
August and now I have this to deal with
so it's it's gonna let's see and then
this is also afternoon I do better in
the morning
so you know tonight cohousing so lots
going on and yet nothing going on just
making a video because that's what I've
committed to doing and I really didn't
want to make one I almost was inside
can't see myself yeah you don't need to
make one but no I do because it's a
Thursday and even though my child is
home and she normally isn't home alone
making the videos I made this equipment
for a reason I don't know but that
reason it's at the moment cuz I bring it
it's way too exhausted to think of what
that is but just to put myself out there
to the universe and one of these days
I'm gonna be able to explain my global
cooperative in a way that the right
person hears it and hopefully they're
able to explain it to more people in a
better way than I can but maybe they can
stand together and we'll figure out
another way and we'll have the third
person and a fourth person and as people
come on board willingly and
enthusiastically we will change this
planet and there's nothing besides maybe
being a mom but I mean this is part of
me being a mom that I can do that's more
important it not and honoring that even
in a society that doesn't honor that
that when you're not working for a
living when you're on disability when
you're doing other things you're I don't
know considered less than
and I'm working to change that in my own
subconscious I think it has shifted
greatly in the last year especially in
the last six months or so realizing that
my mental labor of constantly thinking a
DB and not being able to turn it off is
labor and although I'm not able to maybe
physically put in as much labor as other
people a lot of the time and I'm still
dealing with that I'm still very much
believe I have my disability and my
illnesses are limitations for a reason
and they're either going to teach you
what they're here to teach me and
they'll dissolve and go away or they're
here permanently and there's something I
have to deal with and I have to kind of
be okay with both of those options not
give up on trying to find a solution and
trying to have more energy but also not
living in that future where that's gonna
happen I have the energy I have I have
the life I have and to just keep doing
what I can on a day-to-day basis and
being kind to myself that where I'm at
here's where I'm at and this is pretty
close to five minutes of me rambling so
I will see you all tomorrow happy
Thursday